knownhost.com 2018-12-22

# Privacy Policy For KnownHost - Our Commitment To You

## Information

When you sign up for our service, we will ask you to provide contact information such as your name, address, telephone numbers, e-mail addresses, and payment information such as credit card number and expiration date.

We may ask you to complete user surveys, and to provide certain demographic information, such as age, gender, special interests, etc. You do not have to provide this type of information to use our service if you do not want to.

If you contact us for customer support, we may also ask you for information about your operating system, software and other technical matters.

When you visit our Web site we will capture your IP Address, time of and duration of visit, and time and duration of the pages on our Web site that you view. We may tie this information to the personally identifiable information we have about you.

We will also place a cookie that will identify you to us as a repeat visitor or a customer when you visit our Web site. See "What is a Cookie" below. We may tie this cookie to the personally identifiable information we have about you.

If we send you an e-mail, we may include a marker that will allow to identify e-mail that is opened and viewed.

## Use of Personally Identifiable Information

We will use your personally identifiable information only as follows:

  * For payment purposes and to provide customer support;
  * To announce special offers or provide other information from time to time via e-mail. We may also send e-mail announcing special offers by our third parties, but we will not provide the third parties with your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information. If you do not wish to receive these e-mails, you may opt out of future e-mails at any time by following the instructions included in the e-mail.
  * To improve our service and the marketing of our service. For example, we may use the information we gather from user surveys, demographic data, and web site visits to help us improve or target our Web site and customize your visit.

We will not provide any personally identifiable information about you to any other person other than:

  * a law enforcement or regulatory agency at their request;
  * a person or company who acquires our business;
  * third parties who perform services on our behalf (such as payment processing), subject to the third party agreeing with us that it will keep your personally identifiable information confidential;
  * as otherwise needed to protect or enforce or rights or the rights of others.

We absolutely do not transfer or sell your information for inclusion on third party e-mail or other marketing lists.

We will never disclose your data to any third party unless we are required to do so by court or administrative order. Each party retains all right, title and interest in its data, information and intellectual property rights, and nothing in this Agreement is intended to transfer or diminish such rights. We claim no ownership or control over any content submitted, posted or displayed by you on or through our services.

## Use of Non-Personally Identifiable Information

We may share aggregate statistical data about our customers with third parties, such as advertisers or suppliers. This aggregate statistical data will not identify you personally.

## What is a Cookie

A "cookie" is an alphanumeric identifier that is unique to your browser. The cookie will identify your browser to us when you visit our web site so that we may customize your visit.

## Security of Your Information

We store your personally identifiable information and payment information in protected environment in encrypted format.

## Children's Privacy

Our service is not available to children under the age of 13, and we will not intentionally maintain information about anyone under the age of 13.

## Additional Terms specific to citizens of the European Union

The following terms apply to direct customers of KnownHost LLC who are current European Union citizens residing within the European Union.

## EU-U.S. Privacy Shield

KnownHost LLC complies with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information transferred from the European Union to the United States. KnownHost LLC has certified to the Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles. If there is any conflict between the terms in this privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. KnownHost is under the jurisdiction of the FTC and subject to its investigatory powers. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification, please visit https://www.privacyshield.gov/

## Collection of Information

KnownHost obtains and stores specific account information such as your name, address, telephone numbers, e-mail addresses, and payment information such as credit card number and expiration date. We may also record your IP address and any communications addressed to us via email, or the online support portal. We use these records to process billing and technical support for services provided to you. From time to time we will also use this information to notify you of new products or offerings as well as communicate any new discounts or changes in your services. We share limited information with companies who conduct analytical and marketing suppression, such as Google, Adroll and Facebook, this helps us understand how people are using our website and services.

## Access of Information

A user may access and update their information by logging into our client portal located at https://my.knownhost.com . For instructions on how to access or update your information please visit our knowledge base articles here: https://www.knownhost.com/wiki/my-knownhost . For any other questions or concerns you may contact our billing department by emailing billing@knownhost.com

## Opt Out Clause

If you wish to opt out of any non-essential emails, such as notices of new products or services you may contract us with this request via email to sales@knownhost.com

## Complaints and Dispute Resolution

KnownHost LLC is committed to upholding the EU-EU Privacy Shield agreement. For European Union citizens any complaints regarding your privacy in regards to our collection and use of your information please contact us one of the following ways. We will perform this service at no charge.

Email: privacy@knownhost.com

Mail:  
KnownHost LLC Attn: Privacy Policy  
1379 Dilworthtown Crossing  
Suite 214  
West Chester, PA 19382  
United States  

If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint, or if your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed, you can also submit your complaint to PrivacyTrust, an independent third party. Visit https://www.privacytrust.com/drs/knownhost to file a complaint. You will not have to pay to use this service.

Finally, as a last resort and in limited situations, EU individuals may seek redress from the Privacy Shield Panel, a binding arbitration mechanism.

## Transfer to Third Parties

In cases of onward transfer to third parties of data of EU individuals received pursuant to the EU-US Privacy Shield, KnownHost LLC remains liable.

## Data Retention

KnownHost LLC will retain your information for a minimum of the period of time required by law. After you no longer have active services your account information is retained for a minimum of 7 years for regulatory reasons.

## Merger or Acquisition

In the event of a merger or acquisition all personal data and information will be transferred to the new entity.

## Policy Date

This policy was updated June 27th, 2018.
